Jeff Gold Collection ARC.0037
Library and Archives
- Series III: Art Collins Files, 1975-2005, undated
  - Subseries 3: Rolling Stones Records
    - The Rolling Stones
      - 1981 tour documents (Box AC3, Folder 13, Box OS2, Folder 3)
      - Howard Bloom status report for Bill Wyman, 1981 (Box AC3, Folder 14)
      - Lyrics, undated (Box AC3, Folder 15)
        photocopied from a book
      - Photographs, 1977-1981 (Box AC3, Folder 16-18, Box OS2, Folder 3)
      - Sessions, 1979-1980, undated (Box AC3, Folder 19)
      - Sheet music, 1967-1981 (Box AC3, Folder 20)
        includes book proof
      - Tours, general, 1975-1981 (Box AC3, Folder 21)
      - General documents, 1977-1983 (Box AC4, Folder 1-2)
    - Romeo, Max, 1980-1981 (Box AC4, Folder 3)
      contract
    - Royalties, 1977-1984 (Box AC4, Folder 4-11)
    - Tosh, Peter, 1978-1981 (Box AC4, Folder 12-14, Box OS2, Folder 3)
- Series IV: Ralph Gleason Files, 1949-1981, undated
  Books and periodicals owned by Gleason have been transferred to the library collection. A list of titles is available upon request.
  Custodial History
  Jeff Gold purchased the materials in Series IV: Ralph Gleason Files from Toby Gleason.
  Series IV: Ralph Gleason Files span the years 1949-1981, with the majority of files dating from the 1960s and early 1970s (Gleason died in 1975; any item dated later is an anomaly). The arrangement of this Series is alphabetical by artist or subject. Of particular note in this Series are his files on the subject of payola in the music industry, the psychedelic music scene in San Francisco (as represented by Jefferson Airplane), and Hank Williams, with whom he conducted an extensive interview in 1953. Many of the files contain newspaper clippings, some of which are annotated. Occasionally a file contains correspondence to Gleason, such as that from John Bryan, or notes in Gleason's hand. The last file in the series, "Various artists and subjects", includes a page of notes found in Gleason's copy of Song and Dance Man: the Art of Bob Dylan, and notes from an event featuring Timothy Leary; the contents of this file are also arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Alice Cooper, 1969-1971 (Box RG1, Folder 1)
  - Allman Brothers, 1969-1981 (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 1, Box RG1, Folder 2)
    item from 1981 found with folder, but not added by RJG
  - The Animals, 1964-1967 (Box RG1, Folder 3)
  - Baez, Joan, undated (Box RG1, Folder 4)
  - The Band, 1968-1973 (Box RG1, Folder 5)
  - The Beach Boys, 1966-1971 (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 2, Box RG1)
  - The Beatles, 1967-1969, undated (Box RG1, Folder 7)
  - Belafonte, Harry, undated (Box RG1, Folder 8)
    contains one annotated program
  - Berkeley Folk Festival, 1964-1969 (Box RG1, Folder 9)
  - Big Brother and the Holding Company, 1967-1971 (Box RG1, Folder 10)
  - Bowie, David, 1972-1974 (Box RG1, Folder 11)
  - Brown, Arthur, 1968 (Box RG1, Folder 12)
  - Brown, James, 1964-1969 (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 3, Box RG1, Folder 13)
  - Brown, Ruth, 1952, undated (Box RG1, Folder 14)
  - Bryan, John ( Open City), 1968 (Box RG1, Folder 15)
  - Buckley, Tim, 1967-1974 (Box RG1, Folder 16)
  - Burdon, Eric, 1965-1967, undated (Box RG1, Folder 17)
  - Cash, Johnny, 1958-1971 (Box RG1, Folder 18)
  - Country Joe and the Fish, 1967-1970 (Box RG1, Folder 19)
  - Cream, 1967-1969 (Box RG1, Folder 20)
  - Dave Clark Five, 1963-1964 (Box RG1, Folder 21)
  - Davis, Miles, 1962 (Box RG1, Folder 22)
  - Denny, Sandy, 1970-1971 (Box RG1, Folder 23)
  - The Doors, 1967-1970 (Box RG1, Folder 24)
  - Howlin' Wolf, 1964-1969 (Box RG1, Folder 25)
  - Jazz programs, 1950-1976, undated (Box RG3, Folder 1-10)
    Access Restrictions
    Some of these materials are fragile and/or damaged. Special care must be taken when handling these materials.
  - Jefferson Airplane, 1965-1974 (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 4-7, Box RG1, Folder 26-28)
  - Jethro Tull, 1968-1972 (Box RG1, Folder 29)
  - John Edwards Memorial Foundation, 1967-1969 (Box RG1, Folder 30)
  - John Mayall's Bluesbreakers, 1968-1973 (Box RG1, Folder 31)
  - The Kinks, 1964-1969 (Box RG1, Folder 32)
  - Lennon, John (and Yoko Ono), 1971-1974 (Box RG1, Folder 33)
  - Mathis, Johnny, undated (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 8-9, Box RG1, Folder 50)
  - Moby Grape, 1967-1968 (Box RG1, Folder 34, Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 10)
  - Morrison, Van, 1966-1971 (Box RG1, Folder 35)
  - The Move, 1967-1968 (Box RG1, Folder 36)
  - Newport Festivals, 1965-1969 (Box RG1, Folder 37)
  - Nyro, Laura, 1966-1970 (Box RG1, Folder 38)
  - Payola, 1955-1966; 1973 (Box RG1, Folder 39-40)
  - Pentangle, 1969 (Box RG1, Folder 41)
  - Pink Floyd, 1967 (Box RG1, Folder 42)
  - Procol Harum, 1967-1973 (Box RG1, Folder 43)
  - Record catalogs, 1958-1974 (Box RG1, Folder 44)
  - Redding, Otis, 1965-1968 (Box RG1, Folder 45)
  - San Francisco Chronicle, 1960 (Box RG1, Folder 46)
  - Seatrain, 1971-1973 (Box RG1, Folder 47)
  - Simon & Garfunkel, 1966-1974 (Box RG1, Folder 48-49)
  - Sly and the Family Stone, 1968-1972 (Box RG2, Folder 1)
  - Small Faces, 1971 (Box RG2, Folder 2)
  - Soft Machine, 1970-1974 (Box RG2, Folder 3)
  - Sons of Champlin, 1969-1971 (Box RG2, Folder 4)
  - Spooky Tooth, 1969-1970 (Box RG2, Folder 5)
  - Steppenwolf, 1968-1970 (Box RG2, Folder 6)
  - Stevens, Cat, 1967-1974 (Box RG2, Folder 7)
  - Stewart, Rod, 1970-1974 (Box RG2, Folder 8)
  - Toronto Peace Festival (and Montreal), 1970 (Box RG2, Folder 9)
  - United States of America (band), 1967 (Box RG2, Folder 10)
  - Van Ronk, Dave, 1963-1972 (Box RG2, Folder 11)
  - Waters, Muddy, 1967, 1972 (Box RG2, Folder 12)
  - The Who, 1964-1970 (Box RG2, Folder 13)
    includes album inserts to Live at Leeds
  - Wilson, Wes, 1966-1967 (Box RG2, Folder 14)
  - Wonder, Stevie, 1973 (Box RG2, Folder 15)
  - Woodstock, 1969-1972 (Box RG2, Folder 16)
  - Young, Neil, 1971 (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 11)
  - The Youngbloods, 1966-1973 (Box RG2, Folder 17)
  - Various artists and subjects, 1955-1970 (Box RG2, Folder 18)
- Series V: Posters, 1964-2001, undated
  Series V: Posters consists of art used to advertise or depict performing artists and bands from the years 1964 to 2008. The Series is split into three subseries: Subseries 1: Artists contains those posters that feature only one artist; Subseries 2: Multiple Artists primarily documenting concerts with more than one act; and Subseries 3: Subjects for those posters documenting an event or particular subject. All posters are arranged alphabetically, with Subseries 2 arranged by the headliner or artist with top billing.
  - Subseries 1: Artists, 1964-2001, undated
    - Ryan Adams and the Cardinals
      - Rialto, 2008 Jan. 18 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-3, Object 1-2)
      - 2008 January 22, 30-31 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-3, Object 3)
      - Cain's Ballroom, Tulsa, 2008 January 16 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-1, Object 3)
      - The Band, 1975 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-1, Object 1)
        A2001.93.34
    - Alice Cooper (band), 1976 (Object Museum storage)
      A2001.93.40
    - Bay City Rollers, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-3, Object 1)
      A2002.82.234
    - The Beach Boys, Surf's Up promo, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-3, Object 2)
      A2002.82.231
    - The Beastie Boys, Japanese tour, circa 1980s (Object Museum storage)
      A2005.105.14
    - The Beatles
      - Official Beatles Fan Club souvenir, 1968 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-2, Object 6)
        A2002.82.25
      - Capitol Records promo, 1984 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-1, Object 2)
        A2001.93.38
      - Yellow Submarine promo, from Billboard magazine, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-4, Object 1)
    - The Bee Gees, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-5, Object 1)
    - Black Flag, undated (Object Museum storage)
      A2001.93.2
    - Bland, Bobby, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-2, Object 7)
    - Blondie, 1980 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-1, Object 1, Drawer-folder FF.3.3-4, Object 2)
    - Bowie, David
      - 137 Reasons Why..., 1980 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-1, Object 4)
        A2001.93.39
      - David Live promo, 1974 (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-3, Object 5)
        A2002.82.239
      - London concert ad, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-3, Object 6)
      - Original soundtrack from the film Christiane F., 1982 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-1, Object 3, Drawer-folder FF.3.3-3)
        A2001.93.11, A2002.82.231
      - Popfoto magazine pull-out, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-3, Object 4)
      - RCA promo, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-3, Object 7)
      - Warfield, San Francisco, 1997 Sept. 15-16 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-1, Object 10)
    - Brinsley Schwarz, undated (Object Museum storage)
      A2001.93.4
    - Chenier, Clifton, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-1, Object 2)
    - Circle Jerks LP promo, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-4, Object 1)
    - Clapton, Eric, 1974 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-1, Object 7)
      A2001.93.50
    - Cooder, Ry, circa 1972 (Object Museum storage)
      A2004.54.172
      Boomer's Story LP promo
    - Country Joe and the Fish, 1967 (Object Museum storage)
      A2001.93.27
    - Crime, DNA Lounge, 1988 Aug. 28 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-1, Object 12)
    - de la Soul, Stanford University, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-2, Object 14)
      signed and mounted
    - Dead Kennedys, The Sound of Hell Too Close to Home, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-5, Object 12)
    - Devo, circa 1978 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-7, Object 12-13)
      A2004.54.106-A2004.54.107
      Q: Are We Not Men? A: We Are Devo! LP promo
    - Dinosaur Jr., KUSF presents, March 15 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-1, Object 14)
    - The Doobie Brothers, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-5, Object 2)
    - Dream Syndicate, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-5, Object 10)
    - Dylan, Bob
      - Masonic Temple, San Francisco, 1964 Nov. 27 (Object Museum storage)
        A2007.43.1
      - Le Zenith, Paris, France, 1995 March 24 (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-1, Object 1)
    - The Fabulous Thunderbirds, 1979 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-1, Object 8)
      A2001.93.54
    - Fear, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-5, Object 11)
    - Fried, Robert (designer), 1970 Oct. 7-11 (Object Museum storage)
      A2005.105.21
      Phoenix Gallery exhibit, Berkeley, CA
    - The Go-Go's, 1984 (Object Museum storage)
      A2001.93.13
    - The Grateful Dead, Swing Auditorium, Dec. 12, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-3, Object 16)
    - The Gun Club, Fire of Love promo, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-1, Object 4)
    - Harrison, George
      - Gone Troppo promos (3), 1982 (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-1, Object 2-3, Object Museum storage)
        A2001.93.14, A2002.82.243-A2002.82.244
        3rd copy in Museum storage. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
      - The Best of George Harrison promo, 1976 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-2, Object 10, Object Museum storage)
        A2001.93.15, A2002.82.215
        2nd copy in Museum storage. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
    - Hendrix, Jimi
      - Pinnacle reprint, undated (Object Museum storage)
        A2001.93.23
      - General portraits, 1991, undated (Object Museum storage)
        A2001.93.24-A2001.93.25
      - Stone Free: A Tribute to Jimi Hendrix promo, 1993 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-1, Object 9)
        A2001.93.55
    - Jagger, Mick, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-1, Object 5)
    - Jane's Addiction, Universal Amphitheatre, Nov. 28, Dec. 1 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-1, Object 13)
    - Jefferson Airplane
      - Fillmore, San Francisco, 1966 February 2-4 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-5, Object 6)
        A2004.54.162
      - Other Half, Denver, CO, 1967 November 7-8 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-6, Object 8)
        A2004.54.182
    - John, Elton, 1980 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-1, Object 10)
      A2001.93.60
    - Jon Spencer Blues Explosion tour blank, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-2, Object 2)
    - Killing Joke, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-1, Object 6)
    - King, B.B., undated (Object Museum storage)
      A2005.105.1
    - King Crimson, Three Of A Perfect Pair promo, 1984 (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-1, Object 4-5)
      A2002.82.227-A2002.82.228
    - Kraftwerk, 1975 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-1, Object 11)
      A2001.93.53
    - Kweskin, Jim
      - Avalon Ballroom, Dec. 28-30, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-4, Object 10)
      - With Sons of Champlin, Avalon Ballroom, Dec. 8-10, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-4, Object 9)
    - Lead Belly, undated (Box OS3, Folder 2, Object 6)
      A2004.54.139
      Negro Folk Songs LP promo
    - Led Zeppelin
      - Coda (no photo), 1982, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-1, Object 12, Drawer-folder FF.3.2-2, Object 11-13)
        A2001.93.52, A2002.82.209-A2002.82.211
      - Coda (with photo), 1982, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-2, Object 14, Drawer-folder FF.3.1-1, Object 13)
        A2001.93.41, A2002.82.223
    - Lewis, Furry, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-2, Object 6)
      foam core base
    - Lightfoot, Gordon, 1967 (Object Museum storage)
      A2005.105.3
      New Penelope Club, Montreal
    - Little Feat, 1981 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-4, Object 1, Drawer-folder FF.3.1-1, Object 15)
      A2001.93.48, A2002.82.224
    - Madonna
      - True Blue promos, 1986 (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-1, Object 7, Drawer-folder FF.3.1-2, Object 1)
        A2001.93.42, A2002.82.241
      - Sire Records promotional portrait, 1984 (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-1, Object 8)
        A2002.82.240
    - Marley, Bob
      - Cotillion Records promo for Chances Are, 1981 (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-3, Object 8, Drawer-folder FF.3.1-2, Object 2)
        A2001.93.37, A2002.82.238
      - Island Records promo, 1977 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-2, Object 3)
        A2001.93.17
      - Legend promo, 1984 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-2, Object 4)
        A2001.93.45
    - Mayall, John, Shrine Hall, September 6-7 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-2, Object 4)
    - Meat Puppets, SST Records promo, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-4, Object 15)
    - Morrison, Van, undated (Object Museum storage)
      A2001.93.3
    - Moscoso, Victor (designer)
      - The Plastic Explosion and the Plague, 1967 April 14-15 (Object Museum storage)
        A2001.93.31
        Webb's, Stockton, CA
      - Haight-Ashbury "Clean In", 1967 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-7, Object 3)
        A2004.54.203
    - Newman, Earl, 1964 (Object Museum storage)
      A2001.93.19
    - Nirvana, 1993 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-2, Object 5)
      A2001.93.69
    - Nitty Gritty Dirt Band LP promo, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-5, Object 9)
    - Obey, Ebenezer (Nigerian independence), Fillmore, 1985 October 26 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-2, Object 1)
    - Parton, Dolly, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-3, Object 9)
      A2002.82.233
    - Pearl Jam
      - Mookie Blaylock, Inspector Luv, The Ride Me Babies, 1991 March 1 (Object Museum storage)
        A2005.105.22
        The Off Ramp, Seattle
      - Mookie Blaylock, undated (Object Museum storage)
        A2005.105.24
        O.K. Hotel, Seattle
    - Pink Floyd, 1973 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-2, Object 6)
      A2001.93.43
    - The Police, 1981 (Object Museum storage)
      A2001.93.16, A2001.93.18
    - Pop, Iggy (and the Stooges)
      - Promo for show at 40 Watt Club, 2001 (Object Museum storage)
        A2005.105.13
      - Bookie's Club 870, Detroit, 1980 September 22-27 (Object Museum storage)
        A2005.105.15
        reprint
      - The Stooges with the Flaming Groovies at The New Old Filmore, 1970 May 15-16 (Object Museum storage)
        A2005.105.16
      - "Lust for Life" promo, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-1, Object 9)
      - Soldier promo, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-1, Object 10)
    - Presley, Elvis
      - Charro, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-3, Object 1)
        A2002.82.6
      - Double Trouble, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-3, Object 2)
        A2002.82.2
      - Elvis On Tour, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-3, Object 3)
        A2002.82.4
      - Harum Scarum, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-3, Object 4)
        A2002.82.7
      - Kid Galahad, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-3, Object 5)
        A2002.82.10
      - Kissin' Cousins, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-3, Object 6)
        A2002.82.3
      - Live a Little, Love a Little, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-3, Object 7)
        A2002.82.1
      - Speedway, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-3, Object 8)
        A2002.82.9
      - Spinout, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-3, Object 9)
        A2002.82.11
      - Stay Away Joe, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-3, Object 10)
        A2002.82.5
      - The Trouble With Girls, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-3, Object 11)
        A2002.82.8
    - The Pretenders, 1980 (Object Museum storage)
      A2001.93.22
    - Procol Harum, undated (Object Museum storage)
      A2001.93.7
    - Quicksilver Messenger Service, University of San Francisco, April 15, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-3, Object 11)
      poster appears to be double printed, with information about a show on April 14th
    - R.E.M.
      - Life's Rich Pagent promo, 1986 (Object Museum storage)
        A2001.93.57, A2001.93.63
      - Document promo, 1987 (Object Museum storage)
        A2001.93.61
      - In Time concert, Avalon Hollywood, 2003 October 29 (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-4, Object 3)
    - Raitt, Bonnie
      - Tour blank, circa 1970s (Object Museum storage)
        A2005.105.12
    - Red Hot Chili Peppers
      - Amsterdam, February 20 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-1, Object 5)
      - Austin, Houston, March 9, March 11 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-1, Object 6, Drawer-folder FF.3.5-4, Object 7)
      - Black and white image of band holding a fish, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-5, Object 7)
      - Californication promo banner, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-5, Object 1)
      - Fillmore
        - April 7, 1989 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-1, Object 7)
        - September 15-16, 1989 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-1, Object 8)
      - Live '88 [German], 1988 (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-5, Object 5)
      - Rockpalast featuring George Clinton and other artists, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-5, Object 6)
      - Self-titled debut album promo, 1984 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-2, Object 7)
        A2001.93.49
      - Tour poster, 1998 September (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-1, Object 11)
      - With Rollins Band, Feb. 23 [German], undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-5, Object 8)
    - Reed, Lou, 1982 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-5, Object 3)
    - The Rolling Stones
      - Europe, 1970 (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-5, Object 4)
      - "Jumpin' Jack Flash" promo, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-2, Object 10)
      - Sucking in the Seventies promo, 1981 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-2, Object 8)
        A2001.93.36
      - Tattoo You promos, 1981 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-2, Object 9-10)
        A2001.93.66-A2001.93.67
    - Ronstadt, Linda, 1974 (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-3, Object 2, Drawer-folder FF.3.1-2, Object 11)
      A2001.93.51, A2002.82.232
    - Run-DMC, 1986 (Object Museum storage)
      A2001.93.21
    - The S.H.F. Band, 1975 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-2, Object 12)
      A2001.93.62
    - Santana, 1976 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-2, Object 13)
      A2001.93.46
    - Scritti Politti, Cupid and Psyche 85 promo, 1985 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-1, Object 12)
    - The Second Coming, circa 1966-1967 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-4, Object 17-18)
      Berkeley-based band, featuring Mike Lafferty, David Lieberman, and Vic Smith.
    - Sex Pistols, 1984 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-2, Object 14)
      A2001.93.56
    - Simon, Paul, 1975 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-3, Object 1)
      A2001.93.35
    - Smashing Pumpkins, Warfield, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-4, Object 4)
    - Smith, Patti, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-1, Object 13)
    - Sonic Youth, Fillmore, Nov. 15, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-4, Object 14)
    - Springsteen, Bruce
      - General promo, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-5, Object 3)
      - The Roxy, 1975 October 16-19 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-3, Object 2)
        A2001.93.32
    - Steely Dan, Gaucho promo, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-2, Object 3)
      A2002.82.226
    - Stevens, Cat
      - Majikat American tour, 1976 (Object Museum storage)
        A2005.105.18
    - Stills, Stephen, 1970 (Object Museum storage)
      A2001.93.20
    - Stray Cats, Built for Speed promo, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-2, Object 4)
      A2002.82.242
    - T. Rex
      - Marc Bolan portraits, 1973, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-1, Object 5, Drawer-folder FF.3.3-2, Drawer-folder FF.3.2-2, Object 4)
        A2002.82.236
      - Tanx promo, 1973 (Object Museum storage)
        A2001.93.9
      - Tyrannosaurus Rex skeleton, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-1, Object 6)
    - Talking Heads
      - Little Creatures promo, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-5, Object 2)
      - Naked promo, 1988 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-2, Object 5)
      - Speaking in Tongues promo, 1983 (Object Museum storage)
        A2001.93.8
      - Tour blank, undated (Object Museum storage)
        A2005.105.2
    - Turner, Ike and Tina, 1970 Oct. 30-31 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-6, Object 6)
      A2004.54.180
    - Van Halen, Diver Down promo, 1982 (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-2, Object 6)
      A2002.82.235
    - Van Ronk, Dave, 1967 Apr. 28 - May 7 (Object Museum storage)
      A2005.105.4
      Cafe Au Go-Go, New York
    - Velvet Underground
      - Live MCMXCIII promo, 1993 (Object Museum storage)
        A2001.93.6
      - Andy Warhol presents...Velvet Underground and Nico, the Trip, Los Angeles [reproduction], May 3-18 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-2, Object 9)
    - The Who
      - Fall 1976 tour (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-3, Object 3)
        A2001.93.33
      - Face Dances promo, 1981 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-3, Object 4)
        A2001.93.44
      - Tommy banner, undated (Object Museum storage)
        A2003.27.6
      - The Who By Numbers promo, 1975 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-3, Object 5)
        water-damaged
      - Who's Last promo, 1984 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-3, Object 6)
        A2001.93.59
      - The Kids Are Alright soundtrack, circa 1979 (Object Museum storage)
        A2004.54.118
    - Wilson, Wes (designer), 1967 Oct. 6-14 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-6, Object 2)
      A2004.54.174
      University of California, Berkeley
      Advertisement for a psycheledic poster show
    - Wings, 1976 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-3, Object 7)
      A2001.93.10
    - X, circa 1980s (Object Museum storage)
      A2005.105.46
    - Young, Jesse Colin, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-1, Object 7)
    - Young, Neil
      - American Stars 'n Bars, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-4, Object 5)
      - A Concert Fantasy: Rust Never Sleeps, 1979 (Drawer-folder FF.3.3-2, Object 1, Object Museum storage)
        A2001.93.12, A2002.82.229
    - Youngbloods
      - Avalon Ballroom, 1967 September 15-17 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-3, Object 23)
      - Promo, 1969 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-2, Object 5)
    - Zappa, Frank
      - Zoots Allures, circa 1976 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-2, Object 6, Drawer-folder FF.3.5-1, Object 8)
        A2002.82.89
      - The Mothers of Invention, Freak Out!, undated (Object Museum storage)
        A2001.93.64
      - 1975 tour (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-6, Object 21)
        A2004.54.198
    - ZZ Top, undated (Object Museum storage)
      A2001.93.5
  - Subseries 2: Multiple Artists, 1966-1994, undated
    - 13th Floor Elevators, Sir Douglas Quintet, 1966 September 2-3 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-5, Object 13)
      A2004.54.169
    - Australian bands, general, 1985 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-6, Object 9-15)
      A2004.54.185-A2004.54.191
      all shows at Arts Factory, Byron Bay, Australia
    - Big Brother and the Holding Company
      - With Blue Cheer, Denver, CO, 1967 September 8-9 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-2, Object 3)
      - With the Charlatans and Blue Cheer, Avalon Ballroom, 1967 March 31-April 1 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-3, Object 24)
      - With Bo Diddley, Avalon Ballroom, August 5-6 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-3, Object 25)
      - With Mount Rushmore, November 23-25 (Drawer-folder FF.3.5-3, Object 26)
    - Mike Bloomfield, The Byrds, and Pacific Gas and Electric, 1969 February 6-9 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-7, Object 2)
      A2004.54.202